厄尔  我发现你老兵不死啊
Earl, I noticed you're still alive.
你长寿的秘诀是什么
What's your secret?
靠的是我积极的态度
Well, it's my positive attitude,
还有一点家族遗传
a little bit of genetics,
以及懂得保养自己的身体
and knowing how to take care of your body.
我用荷荷巴
I use Jojoba.
那是什么  乳液之类的吗
What is that, like a lotion?
不  是个叫荷巴的妓女
No, it's a ho named Joba.
她每周会来"保养"我一回
She comes over once a week.
麦克斯  家里收到一个你的包裹
Max, you just got box delivered at home.
我不想要多一个包裹[阴部]
I don't want another box.
光一个我的手就忙不过来了
I got my hands full with this one.
曾几何时  我家的包裹如雪片般飞来
I used to have so many packages delivered to my house,
我爸为了省钱  都直接把联邦快递买了
my dad had to buy Fedex just to save money.
我还记得没有邮政的年代
I remember a time before mail.
你根本不会收到东西
You just didn't get stuff.
不要  我不想要
Nope. I don't want that.
这快递是我妈寄的
It's a delivery from my mother.
她上一次寄送[生育]的东西是我
the last thing she delivered was me,
而我到现在还在收拾她惹的祸呢
and I'm still cleaning up that mess.
你难道都不好奇她寄了什么来吗
Aren't you at least curious what she sent?
除非是个全新的童年
Unless it's a brand new childhood,
否则我没半点兴趣
I'm not interested.
厄尔  帮她保管下包裹吧[抓住阴部]
Here, Earl, hold Max's box.
我可把她当亲闺女  这样不好吧
But she's like a daughter to me.
卡洛琳  我把我的鱼缸带来了
Look, Caroline, I brought in my fish tank,
麦克斯一直说这是我的奥运标准泳池
which Max has been calling my olympic-size swimming pool.
你看吧  阿憨  海平面上的世界大不同啊
See, Han? The world's different above sea-level.
快过来跟它们打招呼
Now, come over here and say hello.
我现在得给鱼打招呼了吗
I'm saying hello to fish now?
我沦落到这般田地了吗
That's where I'm at?
麦克斯  你也来
You too, Max.
我想我的餐厅家庭见见我的鱼儿家庭
I want my diner family to meet my fish family.
我阿姨酗酒程度如鲸鱼吸水
I got an aunt that drinks like a fish.
她可能就在缸里呢
Maybe she's in there.
不对  她开车撞死人被关进牢里了
Oh, no, she's in jail for vehicular manslaughter.
请享受我爱的生态
Please enjoy my ecosystem of love.
永远不许敲鱼缸
Never tap on the glass!
瞧你那只贱肉爪
Just look at that meaty paw of yours.
拍一下里面就是一场地震啊
It's like an earthquake to them.
那是我的珍宝
Oh, there's my prize.
我的品蓝色拟刺尾鲷
The royal blue tang fish.
花了五百块呢
$500.
阿憨  你花钱招妓[蓝刺尾鲷]我不意外
Han, I'm not surprised you have to pay for blue tang,
但五百块贵了点吧
But $500 seems high.
阿憨  荷荷巴一次只要25块哦
Hey Han, Jojoba'll do it for 25.
希望你的鱼在这里过得开心
Well, I hope your fish will be very happy here.
虽然这里没人开心  但也说不准啊
I mean, no one else is, but who knows.
麦克斯  我们走
Let's go, Max.
他绑架了连恩·尼逊的女儿吗
Did Oleg take Liam Neeson's daughter?
我在跟我所有的妞们分手
I'm breaking up with all my ladies
好跟苏菲重新开始
so I can start up again with Sophie.
奥克萨娜这次不再乖乖听话[躺下]
And Oksana's not taking it lying down,
或忍受[撅起屁股]我了
or bent over like she usually is.
没有机会与她见面  太遗憾了
Well, I'm sorry I never got to meet her.
就跟她说你决定跟苏菲...
Just tell her that you and Sophie have decided to be--
乌克兰语的"一夫一妻"怎么说
what's the Ukrainian word for "Monogamy"?
没有这个词
There isn't one.
你要么是丑没人睡  要么就是睡遍天下
You're either ugly or you're sleeping with everyone.
不行  不可以
Uh-uh. No way.
把它留在外面
Leave it out here.
让拆弹小组来拆吧
Let the bomb-squad figure it out.
你难道不想知道她寄了什么给你
Don't you wanna know what she sent you?
说不定里面有钱呢
Maybe there's money in there.
所以你就这么把它丢在走廊
So you're just gonna leave it out in the hall
像客房服务的餐盘一样吗
like a room service tray?
天啊  我曾是有客房服务的人
Oh, my God, I used to have room service.
天啊  我曾是有房间的人
Oh, my God, I used to have a room.
我不想要它进来我们公寓里
Well, I don't want it in the apartment.
这里是正能量与好氛围的场所
This is a place of positive energy and good vibes.
我明天就把它寄回去给她
I'm sending it back to her tomorrow.
一直到我入乱葬岗为安了
I will go to my shallow, unmarked grave
我也不想知道里面是什么
not knowing what's in that box.
麦克斯  你外面有个包裹
Hey, Max, you got a box out here,
里面有只熊娃娃呢
and there's a bear in it!
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
她居然留着这个
She kept that?
我妈怎么会留着这个呢
How did my mom ever keep that?
她连自己的牙都留不住
She can't even keep her teeth.
盒子里装的就是这个吗
That's what was in the box?
一只泰迪·华斯比娃娃吗
A Teddy Ruxpin doll?
你是垃圾破烂熊的订阅会员吗
Are you registered at mustybears.com?
它不是娃娃  那也不是他名字
Not a doll and not his name.
我将其合法改名为熊霸天了
I had it legally changed to T-rux.
找的就是我妈以前请来
I used the same lawyer my mom hired
把我身份改成印第安人的律师
to declare me native American
这样她去赌场就不用停车费了
so she didn't have to pay for parking at the casino.
有足足六个月我接电话都得说
For six months, I had to answer the phone,
我叫"麦克斯·荣耀之足"
"Max proudfoot."
在波兰  我们没有娃娃
You know, in Poland, we didn't have dolls.
我们就租吉普赛小孩
Yeah, we just hired little gypsy kids
然后抱着他们到处遛
and we carried them around.
我租的小孩叫歌吉欧
Yeah, mine was called Gurgio.
我想他好像有一点小儿麻痹
Yeah, and I think uh, he had a little bit of polio.
那玩偶不是会说话吗
Hey, didn't those things talk?
如果有4颗2号电池就可以啊
They did if you had four C batteries.
等等  我好像有
Wait, I think I have some.
当时这还有附泰迪熊的唱歌卡带
Yup, they came with this adorable teddy bear singing cassette,
不用想也知道  我拿石头砸烂它
so of course, I smashed that with a rock
然后自己录了一个
and made my own.
我的歌吉欧不说话
Yeah, my Gurgio didn't talk.
我都不知道他有没有舌头
I'm not sure he had a tongue.
但是他以前会抱我抱得超紧
But he used to squeeze me really tight.
我是到后来才发现  他是35岁的侏儒
And then I found out later, he was 35.
你的床头柜有4颗2号电池吗
You had four C batteries in your nightstand?
从"哪儿"掏出来的
From what?
你还想不想听你的熊说话了
Do you wanna hear the bear talk or don't you?
抱歉  姑娘们
Oh, I'm sorry, girls.
我得去接这个电话
I gotta take this.
是我其中一个要分手的男宠
It's another guy that I'm breaking it off with.
真心希望奥列格值得我如此
I sure hope Oleg's worth it.
我为了他跟一个有多重人格的男人分手
I just dumped a guy with multiple personalities.
他有一重人格能接受
Yeah, and he took it okay,
一重人格不太能接受
and not great,
一重人格超不能接受
and pretty bad.
里面也没有个字条还什么
There's no note or anything.
这箱子就像是个失望之井
This box is really just a well of disappointment.
你妈妈为什么会寄这个给你
Why would your mother send you this?
她为什么会做任何事情呢
Why would she do anything?
她为什么咬了我们的狗
Why would she bite our dog?
她为什么会跟我们的万圣南瓜灯亲热
Why would she make out with our Jack O'lantern?
说实话我也不知道
I don't know.
麦克斯  在这么多年后
Well, Max, she did send you your favorite toy
好歹她把你最爱的玩具寄来了
after all these years.
也许她是想做点事情弥补你
Maybe she's trying to make amends.
还做点事情弥补呢
Oh, make amends?
她连给我做个三明治都做不了
She couldn't even make me a sandwich.
你准备好听了吗
Okay, you ready?
我知道你是啥  但我是啥咧
I know you are, but what am I?
天啊  麦克斯  那是你吗
Oh, my God. Max, is that you?
那是小麦克斯的声音吗
Is that your little Max voice?
朋友快闪  同志退开  我要大开杀戒啦
Careful, I'm about to open up a can of whoop ass.
真的是你  你当时多大啊
It is you! How old were you there?
十岁  "大开杀戒"是我当年的招牌语
Ten. "Whoop ass" was kind of my thing.
现在还是
Still is.
我一直都知道你曾经也是个小孩
I mean, I guess I always knew you were a little kid once,
但直到听到了  我才能想象出画面
but I couldn't picture it till I heard that.
就像在真实发生前
Like I couldn't picture me eating fruit
我也想象不出我在加油站吃水果的画面
from an Exxon station till I did that.
你们准备好点餐了吗
So, are you two ready to order?
我要一份火鸡三明治加薯条
Oh, yeah. I'll have the turkey club with fries.
所以你才会是单身狗  瑞塔
This is why you're single, Rita.
我不是单身狗  我嫁给了你爸爸呢
I'm not single. I'm married to your father.
我爱你  但你别逼本宫也学你一样啊
I love you, but stop pushing your lifestyle in my face.
给本宫来份色拉  酱放小碟子里
I'll have the salad. Dressing on the side.
这必须的
Obvs.
明显的  必须的
Obvs, obvs.
我要把熊霸天寄回去给我妈
Well, I'm sending T-rux back to my mother.
把它放进我在阿憨办公室里找到的空盒子
He's going right into this empty box I found in Han's office.
麦克斯  在你寄回去之前
And Max, before you send it back,
请把电池还给我
I'm gonna need those batteries.
别担心  我完全不想看见你因没电池
Oh, don't worry, I have no desire to see you
转投奶昔搅拌机的怀抱
hugging the milkshake machine.
额  滴  神  啊
Oh...My...God!
那是泰迪·华斯比娃娃吗
Is that a Teddy Ruxpin doll?
瑞塔  本宫想要
Rita, I want that!
埃利奥特  你生日刚过完呢
Your birthday just passed, Elliot.
但我的出柜派对快到啦
But my coming out party is coming up.
那是啥  拉丁女孩成年礼吗
What is that, like a queen-ceanera?
嘴真贱  爱死她了
So bitchy. Love her.
陈年泰迪·华斯比值个五百大洋呢
A vintage Teddy Ruxpin is worth like, $500,
而我妈忙于工作  所以得用钱来买我的爱
And my mom works, so she has to buy my love.
再说一句  我就取消SPA日
One more word, and I'm taking away SPA day.
亲  太绝了吧
That's harsh, honey.
他很迷恋90年代的事物
He's obsessed with the '90s.
你当时都还没出生呢
But you weren't even born.
是啊  都怪她
I know. I blame her.
这货人老珠黄了才终于找到男人
She couldn't find a man till late in life.
跟修脚说再见吧
There go the pedicures.
也跟我的凉拖说再见了
There go my sandals.
虽然我很享受看你们这《威尔和格蕾丝》
As much as I love watching Will and Grace,
但这小家伙是非卖品
This guy's not for sale.
我要把它寄回给我妈
I'm sending him back to my mother's place,
而根据罗德岛假释办公室
which, according to the Rhode Island parole office,
她住在大卖场外的流浪汉纸箱小窝
is a cardboard shanty town outside of Big Lots.
这是本宫的名片  明人不说暗话
Well, here's my card. And let's face it,
你长了一张很缺钱的脸
you look like you could use $500.
嘴真贱  爱死他了
So bitchy. Love him!
有人出价五百块买熊霸天呢
I was just offered $500 for T-rux
就是那个儿童版的安德森·庫珀
from baby Anderson Cooper.
他还有名片啊
He has cards?
我居然嫉妒一个九岁小屁孩
I'm jealous of a nine-year-old?
我沦落到这般田地了吗
That's where I'm at?
虽然我的确很想要那五百块
Hey, as much as I would like that $500,
我不能让我妈觉得这只小熊
My mother doesn't get to think this bear
足以弥补我不幸的童年
gets to make up for my childhood.
没这么容易就放过她
She doesn't get off that easy.
我们曾共睡了一张沙发床九个月呢
Trust me, we shared a pullout couch for nine months.
女孩们  能过来一下吗
Girls, can I see you over here?
真不敢相信又得跟那些鱼说话了
I can't believe we have to talk to the fish again.
我也不敢相信麦克斯还没把阿憨塞进鱼缸
I can't believe Max hasn't put Han in the tank yet.
麦克斯  卡洛琳  以后每天晚上
Max, Caroline, every night from now on,
我要你们拿着这网子  扫过水面
I need you to move the skimmer along the top of the water
把里面的漂浮物捞出来
and take out the floating matter.
阿憨  还记得餐厅的屎永远不用我清吧
Han, you know I'm off diner poop patrol for life
我上次帮餐厅清理了老年顾客留下的...
after I had to clean the booth where the senior left...
且称呼留下的是"清宫秘屎"吧
well, we'll just call it an elderberry.
卡洛琳  麦克斯不做  那就你做吧
Well, Caroline, Max said no, so you have to do it.
在你的鱼面前很霸气啊  阿憨
Han, you're kind of a baller around your fish.
好吧  速战速决
All right, I'm gonna do this fast.
速进速出
Get in and get out--
就跟有鸟在我们浴室里那样
Same thing I do when that bird is in our shower.
麦克斯  上菜
Pick up, Max.
听我说  我遇到真命天女了
Look, I'm calling to tell you I met somebody else
所以才打给你说分手
so I'm breaking up with you.
让你母亲也接一下电话  我也得跟她分手
Now put your mother on. I'm breaking up with her too.
我真不敢相信
I can't believe this.
我是鱼的沙滩男仆
I'm a cabana boy for fish.
我想我现在可以在我简历上的
I guess now I can add "Fish poop remover"
"最高法院实习生"后加上"鱼粪清洁员"
to my resume next to "Supreme court intern."
我感觉最后那下里面有鱼
I feel like there was a fish in that last one.
没错
Yup.
惨了  是贵的那只
Oh, no, it's the expensive one!
标准的我  净挑贵的
That's so me.
我还以为你会在
I really didn't expect to see you
30岁过后才开始翻垃圾
digging through garbage till you were 30.
它还活着
It's still alive!
我得帮它保持湿润
I need to keep her wet.
全身沾满金枪鱼肉  它心灵会严重受创吧
Oh, covered in tuna, that's gotta be traumatic for it.
我有种它被冲走了的感觉
I feel like it went down the drain.
我发誓是场意外
It was an accident. I swear.
我超爱鱼  我永远不会伤害它们
I love fish. I would never hurt one.
除非你算上吃寿司
Unless you count eating sushi,
那我就是开鱼膛手杰克了
'cause then I'm like Jack the ripper.
卡洛琳  事情都如鱼得水一般顺利吗
Caroline, are things going swimmingly?
杰克  他在跟你说话呢
Jack, he's talking to you.
是啊  如鱼得水
Oh, yeah. Swimmingly.
尤其是那条蓝色的
Especially the blue one.
它游进自己的小鱼窝了
He went in his little house.
它不喜欢在小伙伴们面前"上厕所"
He doesn't like to use the restroom in front of his friends.
是啊  它性子跟我很像
Yeah, we're a lot alike.
谢谢你这么快就跟我们见面
Thank you so much for seeing us so quickly.
别客气  你们在这里等吧
Sure, you guys can just wait in here.
埃利奥特马上就练完普拉提了
Elliot's finishing up with his pilates.
就当帮自己个忙
Do yourselves a favor.
夸他核心肌肉看起来很紧实
Tell him his core looks tight.
麦克斯  很抱歉你要为了我
Max, I'm so sorry you have to sell T-rux
把熊霸天卖掉  换钱买金鱼
for the fish money because of me.
跟我的铁拳说去  我的脸在不爽着呢
Talked to the fist, because the face is pissed.
我居然要受一只熊的气
I'm getting attitude from a bear?
我沦落到这般田地了吗
That's where I'm at?
真不敢相信他收集了这么多来自90年代的东西
I can't believe all this stuff he has from the '90s.
真不敢相信他要开个派对才出柜
I can't believe he has to have a party to come out.
那小子出了柜门十万八千里了
That kid came out, out.
他的脐带是一条古驰基皮带
His umbilical cord is a Gucci belt.
瞧瞧这些玩偶
Oh...These toys!
感觉就像在回顾我的童年
This is like looking back at my childhood
但当年彩虹仅仅是彩虹  不是同志象征
but, you know, a time before Rainbows became political.
天啊  我的天啊
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
我的上帝啊
Oh, my god.
巨型芭比娃娃
A My Size Barbie!
我当年有十个呢
I had ten of these.
不过不是拿来玩  是拿来当我的替身
Not to play with, they were used as decoys
以防我被劫持嘛
in case of a hostage situation.
现在你整个人生都被劫持了
And now your whole life's a hostage situation.
抱歉我来晚了
Sorry I'm late.
我和我的教练基里一聊起电视
My trainer, Gary, and I got derailed
《橘子郡贵妇的真实生活》就打不住了
talking about The Real Housewives of Orange County.
你的核心肌肉看起来很棒
Your core looks really good.
本宫知道  亲爱的
I know, honey.
我去拿支票簿  跟奥尔森姐妹娃娃打个招呼
Now while I get my check book, say hello to the Olsens.
你有很多玩具啊
You got a lot of toys.
我像你这么小的时候  我只有这个
When I was a girl your age, I only had this.
娘娘  能恩准我跟巨型芭比娃娃玩会儿吗
I don't suppose I could play with My Size Barbie for a second.
你的眼神在说"不行  贱婢"
I feel like that's a "No, bitch."
我说的不只是这些玩偶
I'm not--I'm not just talking about the toys.
你的房间布置得也很屌
You got a pretty sweet set-up.
外面那位好心女士  不但给你想要的一切
That nice lady out there, giving you everything you want,
还悉心照顾你
taking care of you.
妈不都这样吗  谁没有啊
She's just a mom. Everyone has one.
有的人没有  他们只有霸气的熊
Not really. Some people just have bad ass bears.
麦克斯  你确定要这样做吗
Max, are you sure about this?
这是你童年唯一拥有的东西
This is the only thing you have from your childhood.
才不是呢
Not true,
我的头盖骨还拥有个圆头锤砸的坑
I have a dent in my skull from a ball-peen hammer.
之后我再也没敢在播《三人行》时换台
The last time I change the channel during Three's Company.
我们能不能速战速决  把熊卖给我
Can we fast forward this to me having the bear
你们俩快走人
and you two leaving?
好的  给你  反正也不重要
Okay, just take it, it doesn't matter.
不  麦克斯  这很重要
No, Max. It does matter.
我们不卖了
We're not selling this.
他的玩偶这么多呢
He has enough toys.
我想摸一下真人大小的芭比娃娃都不行
I mean, all I wanted to do was touch the life-size barbie.
我知道这是怎么回事了
Okay, I see what's happening.
跟我买豆豆娃的情况一样
I've been down this road with the Beanie Babies.
那只熊我出到600美元
I'll give you 600 for the bear.
-成交  -不行  麦克斯
- Sold. - No, Max!
那可是你的童年
That's your childhood.
-700美元  -成交
- 700. - Sold!
不行  麦克斯
No, Max!
卡洛琳  我的童年不值700美元
Caroline, my childhood is not worth $700.
我妈最多给过我40块
The most my mother ever got for me was 40 bucks
和一杯超大杯汽水
and a Big Gulp.
娃娃里面住着"童年的你"呢  麦克斯
But that's "little you" in there, Max.
她是无价之宝啊
And she's priceless.
她的声音会被洗掉  取而代之的是
And she's about to erased and taped over
《冰雪奇缘》的原声带
by the soundtrack from Frozen.
《冰雪奇缘》
Frozen?
你以为本宫是一年前的小屁孩吗
Who am I? Me, a year ago?
不行  不能卖给你
No. Can't have her.
那另外一个小屁孩该怎么办
Well, what are we gonna do now about the other child?
我们餐厅那个
The one in the diner?
我猜他只能学着成长了
Well, I guess he's just gonna have to grow up.
成长  你觉得如果他有这能力
Grow up? You think if he had that ability,
他还会是现在这幅样子吗
he wouldn't have used it yet?
什么情况  熊不卖了吗
So what-- no bear?
小公主
Oh, please!
你命中注定会有"熊"男的  相信我
You'll have a bear in your life. Trust me.
麦克斯
All right, Max.
你会帮我告诉他  对吧
You're gonna help me tell him, right?
你喜欢告诉他坏消息
You like giving him bad news.
不对  我喜欢告诉他的坏消息是
No, I like giving him bad news about
他有多矮  头有多大
how he's short and has a big head.
是好玩的坏消息
You know, fun bad news.
好消息
Exciting news!
我给小鱼们买了新家
I got the fishies a new house!
价格超便宜  因为这是止赎屋
I got it cheap. It was a foreclosure.
阿憨  我们能去那边卡座说句话吗
Uh, han, can we talk to you over there in the booth--
最边上那个卡座
the far booth?
不能等吗  我想把新的公寓放进去
Can it wait? I want to put in the new condo
好让麦克斯不再喊我贫民窟主
so Max will stop calling me a slum lord.
等等再放吧
Oh, that can wait,
反正那几条鱼哪儿都不去
I mean, those fish aren't going anywhere.
除了那条蓝的  它绝对是在玩
Except for the blue one, who's definitely playing
某种变态的躲猫猫游戏
some kind of twisted game of hide and seek.
是啊  他可喜欢那个小屋子了
Oh, yeah, he loves that little house.
他一定会更喜欢这个的
He's going to love this one even more.
麦克斯  你也过来坐吧
Max, can you join me?
我正忙着服务顾客呢
I'm pretty busy waiting on tables right now.
好吧  发生什么大事了
Okay, what's going on?
麦克斯这辈子从未服务过任何顾客
Max has never waited on a table in her life.
麦克斯  你快给我过来
Max, I need you over here.
我要把这个烤芝士三明治端过去
I'm just putting down this grilled cheese
因为我怕它会凉了
'cause I don't want it to get cold.
她吓到我了
Now I'm freaking out!
麦克斯  不许这么对我
Max, don't do this to me.
我知道你把尸体埋在哪儿  真的那种尸体
I know where the bodies are buried, literally.
我每隔六个月都会换地方啊
I move them every six months.
说吧  什么事
Well, what is it?
阿憨  人生中有时候
Han, sometimes in life,
会发生一些你不想发生的事情
things happen that you don't want to happen.
我知道
Yes.
即使很难面对
And even though it's hard, you know,
你也要坚强面对
you just have to face up to it.
应该吧
I suppose.
老天  这难度系数太高了
Oh, dear god, this is rough.
我要说...
And, well...
阿憨  我真的不想告诉你
Han, I don't wanna have to tell you this,
我知道你肯定不想听到这个消息
I know this is the last thing you ever want to hear--
你就直说吧
Oh, just say it!
卫生棉条机又坏了是吗
The tampon machine is broken again.
晚点我会戴眼罩进女厕所修
Later, I'll get my blindfold and fix it.
想听忠告吗
Word of advice?
等你忍无可忍杀了我时
When you do finally kill me,
记得练练你的表情  别警察一问就露馅
you gotta work on your game face for the cops.
麦克斯  求你了
Max, please.
我不能告诉阿憨我害死他的鱼
I can't tell Han I murdered his fish.
我做不到
I can't.
我也不能告诉他
Well, I can't tell him either.
算了  我来告诉他吧
Oh, hell, I'll tell him.
我是黑人
I'm a black man,
大家早就认定是我干的了
everyone already assumes I did it.
谢谢  真是太感谢你了
Thank you. Thank you so much.
不过是一条鱼嘛  他会没事的
It's just a fish. He'll be fine.
我决定要在小蓝的生日会上
I've decided I'll give Blue the new house
送它一座新房子
at its birthday party later.
今天是那条死鱼的生日吗
It's the damn fish's birthday?
我不说了
I'm out.
你们全部都被邀请了
And you're all invited.
小蓝今天两岁了
Blue's two years old today.
一般它们活不了这么长
They don't usually live that long.
是呀  的确活不了
No, they do not.
够了  我们不能告诉他
That's it, we can't tell him.
即使在阿憨这个年纪
Even at Han's age, which I am guessing
我猜应该在14岁到53岁之间
is somewhere between 14 and 53,
有些孩子就是没准备好成长
some kids just aren't ready to grow up.
那我们该怎么办
What are we gonna do?
我们赶紧跑出去买条新鱼
We're gonna run out and buy a new one.
我们去哪里弄这笔钱
Where are we gonna get the money?
奥列格
Oleg,
还记得两年前你出1000块
you know how two years ago you offered me $1,000
-让我帮你按摩背部吗  -记得
- for a back rub? - Of course.
给卡洛琳500块就行
Caroline will do it for $500.
成交  最后一"举"
Deal. One last hurrah.
必须隔着衣服  只按腰部以上
Over the clothes, above the waist,
我不知道为什么  但你一定要戴套
and I don't know why, but you have to wear a condom.
我找多明尼克·罗塞洛神父
Yes, father Dominic Rosello, please.
他在举行弥撒吗
Oh, he's celebrating mass?
那你能告诉他苏菲·科臣斯基
Oh yeah, could you just tell him that Sophie Kachinski
从今以后要转为一夫一妻了吗
is converting to monogamy?
她不会再"跪"在他的"圣坛"前了
And uh, she won't be kneeling at his altar anymore.
是的  他会懂的
Oh, yeah, yeah, he'll understand.
阿憨呢  他发现了吗
Where's Han and does he know?
没  但我演不下去我有看到那条鱼了
No, but I can't keep pretending I see that fish.
我是个瘾君子  还有点青光眼
I'm a pot-head with a touch of glaucoma.
我只会看到不存在的事物
I'm seeing stuff that's not there.
而不是看到事物的存在
Not seeing stuff that's there.
都把我弄迷糊了
It's confusing.
来吧  快点  快点
Okay. Come on, come on.
塞进去  塞进去  快放进去
Put it in, put it in, put it in.
这一刻我对所有跟你约会过的男人
I have a whole new respect for every guy
心中有了更高的敬意
that's ever gone out with you.
小蓝  生日快乐
Happy birthday, Blue!
生日快乐  生日快乐  小蓝
happy birthday. Happy birthday, Blue.
小蓝呢
Where's Blue?
我一整天没看到她了
I haven't seen her all day.
我刚刚才看见它
I just saw it.
它绝对在里面
Yeah, it was definitely there.
你不会不给小蓝拍拍照
You're not gonna give Blue that cupcake
就要把小蛋糕给它吧
without a photo-op, are you?
拿你i-Pad来拍照啊
Where's your i-Pad?
我刚有看到它  它绝对在鱼缸里
I just saw it. Yeah, it was definitely there.
阿憨  快去啊
Yeah, Han, go!
你需要照片来发到脸书
You need a pic so you can post it on Facebook
或者鱼书之类的啊
or fishbook or whatever.
好主意  来  帮我拿着
Good idea. Here, hold this.
卡洛琳  你今天没这么平
Hey, Caroline, you look less flat.
你终于去做了你早该做的隆乳手术了吗
You finally get that boob job you needed?
我感觉水袋破了
I feel like the baggy broke.
是啊  隆乳材料贪便宜  就是这后果
Yup, that's what happens when you get the cheap implants.
天啊  我的胸罩里
Oh, my God, there is definitely something
绝对有东西在动
moving around in my bra.
这么久违的感觉你还认得出  这是好事
Well, it's good you can still recognize that feeling.
就在这...  我摸到它了
It's right--oh! Oh! I touched it!
好恶心
Gross!
谁快把手伸到我胸罩里帮帮我
Someone, put your hand in my bra and help me.
为何是现在  我都金盆洗手了
Why now? Now that I'm off the market!
别  别  别啊
No, no, no, no, no, no.
我好怕我不小心把它压死了
I'm afraid I'm gonna squish it and kill it again.
好吧  爬上柜台  让它滑下来进缸里
Okay, just get up on the counter and drop it in the tank.
什么
What?
爬上柜台  打开双腿
Get up on the counter, spread your legs,
就这么让它滑进缸里
And just let it fall into the tank.
其实呢
You know what?
不用按摩背了  这个结束后  我们两清
Forget the back rub. After this, we're square.
鱼缸在腿中间  拉开你的制服
Okay, straddle the tank, pull out your uniform,
让它顺流而下
and let it go.
现在我欠你钱了
Now I owe you money.
就蹲坐在鱼缸上
Just squat over the tank like you're delivering
像要生个鱼宝宝
a fish baby.
我要生个鱼宝宝
I'm delivering a fish baby?
我沦落到这般田地了吗
This is where I'm at?
不许废话  你是沦落到这田地
Stop asking. That's where you're at.
这我真的看到了  没错吧
Okay, now that I saw, right?
卡洛琳  快下来
Caroline, get down!
这不是"那种"派对
It's not that kind of party.
麦克斯  你还是要把熊霸天寄回去吗
Max, you're really still gonna send T-rux back?
在我们受了那个
After we got bullied by a kid
有蒂凡妮·西森抱枕的小屁孩羞辱后吗
with a Tiffani Amber Thiessen pillow?
放轻松  熊霸天在收银台上呢
Relax, T-rux is right over there by the register.
对了  他是我们的首名员工
And by the way, he's our first employee.
每当我们碰到傻逼顾客  他可以说
Anytime we get a bone-head customer, he can say,
"跟我的铁拳说去"
"Talk to the fist"...
"我的脸在不爽着呢"
"'cause the face is pissed."
我只是给我妈寄点东西
I'm just sending my mother something
好感谢她在我孩童时期
to say thank you for everything she gave me
给过我的一切
when I was a child.
好有爱  里面是什么
Aww, what's in there?
屁都没有
Nothing!